

MUHAMMAD AMMAR GHIFARI

Passionate Indie Game Developer

About Me

Having more than 2 years of experience in the world of video game development has made me a more competent and proficient person in video game programming and game design. The experience that I have so far made it easier for me to adapt to the latest video game trends and to be able to build games that are good and enjoyable.



+62 812-2766-6909



magptm04@gmail.com



ammrgif



Arduino

St. Marina Emas Tengah, 60111 Surabaya

Language

IndonesiaEnglish78%

Skills Summary

Game Design 80%
Godot Engine 90%
GDScript 90%
Python 82%
STM32 71%

81%

Experience

Abu Robocon Robotics Team

Surabaya, Indonesia

Mar 2024 - Present

Become a member of the Abu Robocon robotics team in the division that handles robot programming

Brackeys Game Jam 2021.1

Online all over the world

Feb 2021 - Feb 2021

Became one of the participants in the competition and managed to enter the top 70 in the Best Audio category

Game Off 2020

Online all over the world Nov 2020 - Dec 2020

Became one of the participants in the competition and managed to enter the top 100 in the Best Graphics category

Projects

SAY NO TO HUMAN

https://biobinary.itch.io/say-no-to-human

Feb 2021 - Feb 2021

Build an army of zombies and destroy all humans

GunVsMagic

https://biobinary.itch.io/gunvsmagic

Nov 2020 - Dec 2021

GunVsMagic: An Impossible Idea

Education

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya Bachelors of Computer Science Aug 2023 - Present

SMA Negeri 1 Kota Magelang, Magelang Majoring in science Jul 2020 - May 2023